{"data":[{"question":"One of the rooms ________ an air conditioner.","a":"contain","b":"contains","c":"is containing","d":"are containing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express general fact.\u00a0\n- Subject (one of) is singular.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Everyone of the clerks ________ punch the time clock.","a":"has","b":"have","c":"has to","d":"have to","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Each of his assistants ________ the telephone.","a":"answer","b":"answers","c":"is answering","d":"are answering","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express general fact.\u00a0\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Each of the girls ________ the piano.","a":"play","b":"plays","c":"is playing","d":"are playing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express general fact.\u00a0\n- The pronouns each, everyone, every one, everybody, anyone, anybody, someone, and somebody are singular and require singular verbs.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"I wonder why the English ________ on the left hand side of the road.","a":"drive","b":"drove","c":"has driven","d":"had driven","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The: used before an adjective to make it into a plural noun when you are referring to all the people that the adjective describes.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"He ________ the custom was grounded in good sense.","a":"say","b":"said","c":"has said","d":"had said","answer":"2","explain":"\nIn reported speech: \n+ If the reporting verb (i.e. said) is in the past, the reported clause will be in a past form. This form is usually one step back into the past from the original.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"A horse ________ always mounted from the left.","a":"is","b":"was","c":"has been","d":"had been","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense: express a habit (often).\u00a0\n- Subject (a horse) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"There ________ no rule about the movement of traffic before the Pope came to visit Paris.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Simple past tense.\u00a0\n- There is\/was (= have): used when object is singular or uncountable noun.\u00a0\n- There are\/were (= have): used when object is plural noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"Thus a custom ________ born.","a":"is","b":"was","c":"has been","d":"had been","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We often say \"was\/were + born\".\u00a0\n- Subject (a custom) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"},{"question":"There ________ only one place in the whole of England where it ________ legal to drive on the right.","a":"is \/ is","b":"was \/ was","c":"are \/ is","d":"were \/ was","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Simple present tense.\u00a0\n- There is\/ There are: real subject is after \"to be (is, are...)\"- only one place is real subject in this case-= to be- is.\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"21","type":"1"}]}